<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on Ryan&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://ryanwooa.github.io/en/posts/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on Ryan&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 16:37:00 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ryanwooa.github.io/en/posts/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deploy a React project on AWS EC2</title>
      <link>https://ryanwooa.github.io/en/posts/tech/aws&#43;react/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 16:37:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ryanwooa.github.io/en/posts/tech/aws&#43;react/</guid>
      <description>1. Background Recently, I developed a full stack project with friends, including React front-end and Express back-end, stored in a GitHub repository. I want to launch and deploy this project now. For React projects, there are many free deployment platforms, such as Vercel and DigitalOcean. But considering that this project includes both the front-end and back-end, consider deploying them in one place. After consulting many materials, it was decided to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo &#43; PaperMod Customization</title>
      <link>https://ryanwooa.github.io/en/posts/tech/customize_hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 21:01:29 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ryanwooa.github.io/en/posts/tech/customize_hugo/</guid>
      <description>1. UI 1.1 Theme file location adjustment After installing the theme, you can copy the files circled in the following image to the corresponding directory on the site, so that you can customize the style of the blog without affecting the update of the theme. Hugo will prioritize reading files from the site directory when loading, and if not, read files from the theme directory. 1.2 Side Table of Contents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a blog with Hugo and Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://ryanwooa.github.io/en/posts/tech/hugo&#43;papermod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 21:37:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ryanwooa.github.io/en/posts/tech/hugo&#43;papermod/</guid>
      <description>1. Introduction 1.1 What is Hugo Hugo is one of the most popular open-source static site generators. With its amazing speed and flexibility, Hugo makes building websites fun again. 1.2 What is Github Pages GitHub Pages is a static site hosting service that directly retrieves HTML, CSS, and JavaScript files from the repository on GitHub, (optional) runs the files through the build process, and then publishes the website. Users can</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
